Oh, hi. Hey, you've got to try this cheesecake. Oh, you know, I'm not that much of a sweet tooth.
Oh my god, so creamy. Oh my god, that is the best cheesecake I've ever had. Where did you get this?
It was at the front door when I got home. Somebody sent it to us.
Chandler, this is not addressed to you. This is addressed to Mrs. Braverman downstairs.
Thief. I didn't read the box before I opened it and you can't return a box
after you've opened the box. Why not? Because it's too delicious.
Chandler, you stole this cheesecake. That is wrong. No, no, no, it is going to be okay
because Mrs. Braverman is going to send away for a free one and that way we all
win. The only losers are the big cheesecake conglomerate, mama's little bakery.
I feel terrible. I'm a horrible, horrible, horrible person. Well, I'm sorry, what?
I'll be there for you.
All right, I should get going. Big day at work. You know, I'm in a coma,
but today they do this test on me and it turns out I'm not brain dead.
Mr. Smarty Pants, it's just my character that's not brain dead.
Hey, Sophie, you still on for tonight? Absolutely. I'll see you at eight. Okay.
Huh, what's at eight? Oh, I have dinner plans with Joey. We get together about once a month
to discuss the rest of you guys. Wow, did not know that. May I say how lovely you look today?
Duly noted. Oh, so for tomorrow, do you want to rent a car and drive down together or what?
What are you talking about? Because in Franny's wedding, it's tomorrow night. You were invited?
No. I can't believe this. I mean, I knew that mom and dad were invited,
but I thought that was it. I mean, from the ages of seven to nine, Franny and I were inseparable.
Well, maybe since the age of nine, Franny's made some new friends.
Do you want to make some new friends?
Well, it's probably just a mistake. Let me call Aunt Cheryl, okay?
Maybe you are invited and the invitation just got lost in the mail.
Yeah, well, you call her and tell her that, you know, when we were kids,
her precious little Franny tried to undress me several times, okay? And if I hadn't stopped her,
there probably wouldn't even be a wedding to go to.
She tried to undress me, too. I used to undress my cousin, Glenn,
too. Joseph Francis Triviani, are you home yet?
Um, I think he's still out. What's wrong? Well, I'll tell you, Rachel Karen Green.
I had plans with Joey tonight and he left me this note.
Phoebs can't make it. Got a date. Talk to you later. Big Daddy.
Big Daddy? Oh, that's a nickname we were trying out.
Why don't you guys try out Francis?
Francis is a cooler name than Chandler, isn't it?
You know what nickname never caught on? The Rossitron.
Hey. Oh, here's Joseph Francis.
What are you middle-naming me for? I left you a note.
So what? That doesn't give you the right to ditch me.
Hey, you can cancel plans with friends if there's a possibility for sex.
Maybe he's right. That is the rule. Really?
Well, that's what I hear. I've never gotten a chance to actually employ the rule.
Well, I don't accept this rule. When we make plans, I expect you to show up,
okay? I can't just be a way to kill time till you meet someone better.
You know, boyfriends and girlfriends are gonna come and go, but this is for life.
Wow. I'm so sorry. I had no idea it would bother you this much.
Well, it does. Okay, can I make it up to you?
I'm sorry. How about dinner tomorrow night? I'll pay for myself.
Okay, you wore me down.
Hey, Joe, while you're over there, how about another beer for the Rossitron?
Oh, is that back?
Hi. Yeah, the cheesecake came.
They delivered it to the wrong address again.
So, just bring it back downstairs. What's the problem?
I can't seem to say goodbye.
Are you serious? Chandler, we ate an entire cheesecake two days ago, and you want more?
I've forgotten what it tastes like, okay?
It was cheesecake. It was fine. It had a buttery, crumbly graham cracker crust
with a very rich, yet light cream cheese filling.
Wow, my whole mouth just filled with saliva.
You know what? Forget it. We are just hungry. We have not had lunch.
We are just lightheaded. So, let us go out and have lunch and forget about the cheesecake.
Yeah, we'll drop it off downstairs so that we're not tempted.
Good idea. Where do you want to go to lunch?
Mama's Little Bakery, Chicago, Illinois.
Oh, Mel Torme died.
Joey, that paper's like a year old.
Oh, does that mean the Sam Goody sale is over?
Hey. Hey.
Hey.
So, I finally heard back from Aunt Cheryl, and apparently it wasn't a mistake.
There's limited seating in the hall.
Limited seating? I am just one tiny person.
Well, yeah, but she doesn't know that. I mean, the last time she saw you,
you would have turned one of those little wedding chairs into kindling.
Limited seating? Oh, that is such a lame excuse.
It's the reason why she's not inviting me.
What's the big deal? I wasn't even invited to the ceremony, just the reception.
And you know what? If it makes you feel any better, Joan and I will just make an appearance,
and then we'll leave early as a sign of protest.
Joan? Yeah, Joan Tedeschi, my date.
She's an assistant professor in the linguistics department. Tall,
very beautiful, and despite what some people say, not broad-backed.
Wait a minute, you got Ross Geller and guest? I wasn't invited, and you got and guest?
Excuse me, I do have to interrupt on Ross's behalf. I think the rule applies here.
You know, since he has a chance to get on broad-backed.
Not broad-backed.
Dude, I've seen her. She's like a billboard.
Wait a minute, you know what? You're bringing me.
I can't cancel on Joan.
Why not?
Did you not hear me? She's an assistant professor in the linguistics department, okay? They're wild.
Why do you want to come anyway?
Because. She's my cousin. I mean, we grew up together. Family, and I don't know, that's
important to me.
Okay, all right, I'll take you. I'll go call Joan.
Oh, that's nice. Family should be there. This is her wedding. Happiest day of her life.
We'll see.
Well, thank you for lunch.
What? Wait a minute, I didn't pay. I thought you paid.
So apparently, we just don't pay for food anymore.
Do you see what I see?
It's still there.
Mrs. Braverman must be out.
She could be out of town. Maybe she'll be gone for months.
By then, the cheesecake may have gone bad. We don't want her to come back to bad cheesecake.
No, that could kill her.
Well, we don't want that.
No, so we're protecting her.
Well, we should take it.
Yeah, but we should move quick.
Why?
Because I think I just heard her moving around in there.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Do you think that it's inappropriate to wear a white lacy dress to a wedding?
Yes.
Excellent.
Oh, my God, that's David.
David who?
David, the scientist guy, David, that I was in love with.
David who went to Russia and broke my heart, David.
Oh, my God.
Oh, you say someone's name and then they turn around.
Phoebe.
David.
What, what are you doing here?
Aren't you supposed to be in Russia?
Yeah, I'm just, I'm just in town for a conference.
God, you look phenomenal.
Well, yeah.
You look great, too.
Did you get a haircut?
Yeah, well, I got like 30 of them.
Um, look, I got a confession to make.
Um, I was hoping to run into you here.
I didn't know whether I should call or not.
You know, I was only in town for a few days and, you know,
I didn't want to intrude on your life or anything like that.
But I really wanted to see you.
But I didn't know if you wanted to see me.
Well, of course I would want to see you.
I, I think about you all the time.
Really? Because I think about you all the time.
I mean, there's a statue in Minsk that reminds me of you so much.
I mean, um, it's actually of Lenin.
Like, you know, at certain angles.
Yeah.
Anyway, do you want to have dinner, uh, tonight?
Yes.
Oh, no.
Oh, uh, what?
I can't. I can't believe I have plans. I can't.
Can you do it tomorrow night, though?
Uh, no. I, I have to go in a few hours.
I have to be on the red eye.
Well, listen, you know, next time you're in Minsk, uh...
Baby, can I talk to you for a second?
Uh-huh.
What are you doing?
Well, I have plans with Joey tonight.
So? He'll understand.
No, he won't.
And that's not even the point.
Monica, I made a whole speech about how you do not cancel plans with friends.
And now, you know what?
Just because, potentially, the love of my life comes back from Russia
just for one night, I, I should change my beliefs?
I should change my beliefs.
No. No.
No, if I don't have my principles, I don't have anything.
God, you are so strong.
Or I should rush through dinner with Joey and I could meet David at nine.
Oh, my God, that is so good.
I'm full.
And yet, I know if I stop eating this, I'll regret it.
Hey, what do you got there?
Oh, it's, um, it's tofu cake.
Do you want some?
What are you doing tonight?
Dude, dude.
Oh, sorry.
Uh, I got those plans with Phoebe.
What?
Oh, really?
Monica said she had a date at nine.
What?
Tonight?
That's what Monica said.
After she gave me that big speech?
She goes and makes a date with a guy on the same night she has plans with me?
I think she's trying to pull a fast one on Big Daddy.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Dude, dude, dude.
If I took off my pants right now, how would you feel?
Like your cousin, Glenn.
Oh, here.
I think this is us.
Limited seating, my ass.
Let's just see who made the cut.
Hi.
I'm Monica Geller.
How do you know the bride and groom?
Oh, I used to work with Franny.
Used to work with her.
Used to.
I'm her relative, but I didn't get invited.
A blood relative.
Blood.
Stop saying blood to strangers.
From the ages of seven to nine, we were inseparable.
Inseparable.
And I didn't even get invited to this.
Then why are you here?
My brother's date.
I had a date, okay?
Joan Tedeschi.
The linguist.
So, how about you?
How do you know the happy couple?
We went to college with both of them.
And now we live next door.
Okay, you're fine.
You know, you would have liked Joan.
She's very pleasant.
There, there.
Her back looks like that.
That's not broad, is it?
Come on, Joey.
You've got to be ready to order by now.
You know what?
I don't think I like this table either.
Maybe we should move again.
No, we're staying right here.
Excuse me.
We're ready to order.
I don't work here.
Well, then you shouldn't be walking around.
Hey.
Hi.
Are you guys ready yet?
Yeah, uh-huh.
I'm gonna have the green salad with the house dressing.
Water's fine.
And you, sir?
Yeah, this slow-roasted salmon.
Just how slow are we talking?
It's, um, it's already been roasted.
Oh, then no.
Maybe I should hear those specials again.
Oh, Joey, we've heard the specials three times, okay?
There's prime rib, mahi-mahi, and a very special lobster ravioli.
Actually, we're out of the lobster ravioli.
Oh, well, that changes everything.
You know what, Peebs?
Huh?
You were right before.
Friends are so important.
Yeah, I'm very wise.
I know.
Yeah.
You know what I really want?
What?
Is to have a long, long talk.
You know, get Joey out on the open road and really open him up.
Any progress?
Yes.
I will have the lobster ravioli.
Oh, God, Joey, this is taking forever.
What's the rush?
What?
Well, I just said that I have, you know, I have an appointment, and it's very important.
Oh, well, what is it?
Well, it's a date.
A date?
No, no, Peebs, you must be mistaken, because I know you wouldn't schedule a date on the
same night you have plans with a friend.
Come on, Joey, don't make me feel badly about this.
No, I'm gonna.
That's right, yeah, you made me feel really guilty about going out with that girl, like,
like, like I did something terrible to you.
Now, Peebs, you're doing the same thing.
It's not the same thing.
This is totally different.
This is with David.
Remember David, the scientist guy?
Okay, he's very special to me.
Okay, well, my girl from the other night was special.
She was a scientist, too.
She was?
Well, she graduated high school.
Okay, whatever.
You know what?
I don't have time to convince you, because he's only here for four hours, and I'm gonna
go see him.
Fine.
Yeah.
What are you still doing here?
I told you, lobster ravioli.
Hey.
Oh, I was just about to leave.
I didn't think you were coming.
Oh, why wouldn't I miss this?
Well, I'm very glad you're here.
Oh, you're such a gentleman.
Come on, we're going to my place.
Oh.
Are you eating the cheesecake without me?
I will give you a hundred dollars to whistle right now.
How can you eat the cheesecake without me?
Oh, what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna go run and tell Monica?
Are you gonna tell Joey?
No, because then you're gonna have to tell them what we did.
We are dessert stealers.
We are living outside the law.
You know what?
I don't trust you with this cake anymore, and I got it first, and I'm taking it back.
What?
Oh, yes.
No, no, no, no, no, no, you don't.
No, no.
You think I trust you with it?
No, we're gonna split it.
You take half, and I take half.
Well, that's not fair.
You've already had some.
Oh, you know what?
I think Monica would be very interested to know that you called her cheesecake dry and mealy.
What do we use to split it?
Okay.
All right, pick a half.
Well, this side looks bigger.
Uh, there's more crust on this side.
Yeah.
So...
Even if I measure...
Oh, for God's sake, just pick a piece.
All right, I'll pick that one.
So the smaller piece.
Okay, there you go.
Enjoy your half, my friend, but that is it.
No sharing, no switching, and don't come crying to me if you eat your piece too fast.
Oh!
All right, you gotta give me some of your piece.
Oh, no, no.
No switching, no sharing, and don't come crying to me.
I may just sit here and have my cake all day.
Just sit here in the hallway and eat my...
Oh, hey, Aunt Millie.
Isn't it a beautiful wedding?
Yes, yes, it is.
Every time on the lips.
Why? Why on the lips?
Here's Franny.
Won't you be happy to see me?
Now, wait a minute.
You be nice, all right?
I didn't bring you here so you can ambush her.
Franny was the one who found your Playboys and showed them to Mom.
That bitch.
Monica!
What am I doing here?
Why?
Surprised to see me?
Ross brought me.
How do you like that?
Hi, Franny.
Congratulations.
You invite my brother?
You invite my whole family and not me?
Why?
Why wouldn't you want me at your wedding?
What could I have possibly done?
Stuart.
I believe you know my husband.
So it's really a question of who could you have possibly done.
I hate this, but I have to go.
I can't miss my flight.
Are you sure?
I'll bet there's another flight to Minsk in like...
July.
It's really beautiful.
What does it mean?
Please clean my beakers.
I don't get out of the lab much.
I thought it meant I was something else.
Yeah, I...
Well, I really actually wanted to say that,
but I figured I probably shouldn't because, you know,
I have to leave.
No, you're right.
You're right. Don't say it.
I do, though.
I do, too.
Yeah, bye, Phoebe.
Okay, now's not the time, Joey, all right?
You can yell at me tomorrow.
Hey, no, no, no.
I'm not gonna yell at you.
Just, you know, I started thinking about you and David,
and I remember how bummed you were the first time you left.
I just...
Oh, Phoebe, just come in here.
Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay.
The only guy I've ever been crazy about is Wanda Minsk,
and I never...
I may never see him again.
Hey, you know, you could always visit him.
Oh, right, like they're gonna let me have a passport.
If there's anything I can do, whatever you need.
Well, Bud, now, if you could achieve positronic distillation
of subatomic particles, you know, before he does,
then he could come back.
I could give it a shot.
Oh, hey, look, there's a piece that doesn't have fluorine in it.
Stick to your science.
Come on, now.
All right, what do we have?
Oh, wait, I forgot my wrap.
Oh, I'll wait here for you.
I can't go back there.
Why?
Did you see the way that Stuart was staring at me?
I think he still wants me.
Oh, my God.
Just go do it.
All right, wait here.
Hi, sweetie, are you leaving?
Well...
Give us a kiss.
Why?
Why on the lips?